var stages = {
    stage1: {
        data: [{
                "question": "Photoelectric effect is associated with?",
                "options": [
                    "A: Non-Metals",
                    "B: Gases",
                    "C: Metals",
                    "D: Photosynthesis",
                ],
                "ans": "C"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of these is not a JavaScript library?",
                "options": [
                    "A: jQuery",
                    "B: Angular",
                    "C: React",
                    "D: Immutablejs",
                ],
                "ans": "B"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which is a CSS framework?",
                "options": [
                    "A: Popper",
                    "B: Modernizr",
                    "C: Bootstrap",
                    "D: Sass",
                ],
                "ans": "C"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which language is closer to the hardware?",
                "options": [
                    "A: Python",
                    "B: Hash",
                    "C: C++",
                    "D: JavaScript",
                ],
                "ans": "C"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who is the creator of Python?",
                "options": [
                    "A: Guido van Rossium",
                    "B: Brendan Eich",
                    "C: Google Inc",
                    "D: Dan Abrahmov",
                ],
                "ans": "A"
            },
            {
                "question": "Colourless and odourless is the property of?",
                "options": [
                    "A: Calcium",
                    "B: Ammonium",
                    "C: Chlorine",
                    "D: Methane",
                ],
                "ans": "D"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who created the C programming language?",
                "options": [
                    "A: Ken Jones",
                    "B: Dennis Ritchie",
                    "C: Bjarnne Stautroup",
                    "D: Tom Smith",
                ],
                "ans": "B"
            }
        ]
    },
    stage2: {
        data: [{
                "question": "What is the full meaning of PHP?",
                "options": [
                    "A: Hypertext Preprocessor",
                    "B: Pre Hypertext Processor",
                    "C: Page High Power",
                    "D: Power High Page",
                ],
                "ans": "A"
            },
            {
                "question": "In JavaScript which is an abstract data type?",
                "options": [
                    "A: Array",
                    "B: List",
                    "C: Symbol",
                    "D: String",
                ],
                "ans": "B"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which is a PHP framework?",
                "options": [
                    "A: Composer",
                    "B: WebGl",
                    "C: Mongoose",
                    "D: Laravel",
                ],
                "ans": "D"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which is the largest country by population?",
                "options": [
                    "A: Russia",
                    "B: United States of America",
                    "C: China",
                    "D: Japan",
                ],
                "ans": "C"
            },
            {
                "question": "Flourine element is known as?",
                "options": [
                    "A: Halogen",
                    "B: Ester",
                    "C: Rare gas",
                    "D: Ethanol",
                ],
                "ans": "A"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of these is not a framework for building Android application?",
                "options": [
                    "A: React Native",
                    "B: Ionic",
                    "C: Phonegap",
                    "D: Kotlin",
                ],
                "ans": "D"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of these is not a metal?",
                "options": [
                    "A: Calcium",
                    "B: Aluminium",
                    "C: Argon",
                    "D: Sodium",
                ],
                "ans": "C"
            }
        ]
    },
    stage3: {
        data: [{
                "question": "Chai is a tool used for?",
                "options": [
                    "A: Testing",
                    "B: Module bundling",
                    "C: Designing",
                    "D: Data Science",
                ],
                "ans": "A"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which is not used for module bundling and task running?",
                "options": [
                    "A: Webpack",
                    "B: Mocha",
                    "C: Gulp",
                    "D: Grunt",
                ],
                "ans": "B"
            },
            {
                "question": "Tkinter is a python library used for?",
                "options": [
                    "A: Artificial Intelligence",
                    "B: Machine Learning",
                    "C: Desktop development",
                    "D: Mobile development",
                ],
                "ans": "C"
            },
            {
                "question": "Golang was created at?",
                "options": [
                    "A: Facebook",
                    "B: Zeit",
                    "C: Microsoft",
                    "D: Google",
                ],
                "ans": "D"
            },
            {
                "question": "Scrapy is a framework used for?",
                "options": [
                    "A: Web crawling",
                    "B: Game development",
                    "C: Network sniffing",
                    "D: Web development",
                ],
                "ans": "A"
            },
            {
                "question": "Nodejs is usually known for its?",
                "options": [
                    "A: Speed",
                    "B: Efficiency",
                    "C: Simplicity",
                    "D: Asyncronousity",
                ],
                "ans": "D"
            },
            {
                "question": "The largest planet is?",
                "options": [
                    "A: Saturn",
                    "B: Jupiter",
                    "C: Earth",
                    "D: Uranium",
                ],
                "ans": "B"
            }
        ]
    }
}